http://www.stoeltingco.com/privacy

Stoelting Co.
privacy policy
Stoelting Co. sometimes collects information from visitors to this web site. Information is collected for the purpose of responding to visitors’ enquiries (such as name and contact details provided when requesting product information) or for general marketing activities (such as keeping you informed about new products, trade shows or other news via a newsletter). Non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of our servers. Such information may include; the name of the ISP from which you access the internet, the Search Engine and keywords you used to locate this site, the date and time you accessed the site, the internet address of the website from which you enter our site and where you go after you leave our site. This information is used to measure and monitor the use of our site and to improve its content. Data which would personally identify you is known only when voluntarily submitted.
Personal data held by us will not be released to third parties except where such disclosure is required by law.
You may request to see a copy of the personal information we hold about you. A Subject Access Request should be sent in writing and we undertake to reply within 40 calendar days. An original signed request should be sent by mail to our offices marked "Subject Access Request" enclosing a cheque or money order for ¬ 5.00 made out to Stoelting Europe.
You have the right to have your personal data corrected, if inaccurate, or erased if you can show that we no longer have a legitimate reason for retaining the data. We will not charge you for complying with such a request which should be sent in writing to our offices or by email to info@stoeltingco.com marked "Data Correction Request" or "Data Deletion Request", as appropriate. We undertake to comply within 40 calendar days.
We take our security responsibilities seriously and employ the most appropriate physical and technical measures to protect data, including staff training and awareness.
If you have any concerns about the privacy of your data then please write to us or email us at info@stoeltingco.com stating the nature of your concern.
©2020 Stoelting Co.
